Benjamin Jimenez

45 Harrington Street Manchester, M18 8UQ 07709206056 jimenezbenjamin@yahoo.com

Coming from a creative background, but also with experience in customer service, retail, studio/sound and live events, i am very adaptable and keen to learn. I have a large range of transferable skills that would be highly beneficial for this position. I am fluent in French and English.

EXPERIENCE

Royal Mail - Postman

MAY 2019

- Preparing the mail and parcels ready for delivery
- Collection and delivery of mail and packages

Black Pudding Record ltd, London - Company Director

JULY 2015- MAY 2019

- Music production/Recording
- Social media, Press releases and sales.
- Co-hosting live events, tour booking, tour driver/manager.

Self-employed – *Sound Engineer*

APRIL 2012- APRIL 2019

- Recording and producing various artists
- Sound field recordings/live sound engineering

Music & Goods Exchange ltd, London - Sales, Management and

Maintenance

JUNE 2011 - MAY 2012

- Cash/Till handling and banking
- Stock take, pricing and visual merchandising
- General store maintenance

EDUCATION

Comprehensive School Adolphe Chérioux, Vitry-sur-Seine, Île-de-France

B.A.C Science of economics and sociology - JUNE 2002

INTERESTS

I am a vocalist and guitarist in a band and i write my own released music I record music and edit photos using protools, logic and photoshop